A Guide to the Henry Luce Foundation records, Luce Fund for Asian Studies and Luce Fund for Southeast Asian Studies FA1860
Rockefeller Archive Center
Henry Luce Foundation records, Luce Fund for Asian Studies and Luce Fund for Southeast Asian Studies
1987-2010
Rockefeller Archive Center
Henry Luce Foundation
FA1860
3.04 Cubic Feet 8 letter document boxes
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research.
Arrangement
As received.
Scope and Contents
This record group contains files related to the Luce Fund for Asian Studies and the Luce Fund for Southeast Asian Studies. These programs represent the Luce Foundation's commitment to advancing the study of Asia at the undergraduate level.
- Luce Fund for Asian Studies, 1999-2010; 1; 2.28 Cubic Feet 6 letter document boxes
  - Luce Fund for Asian Studies Binder, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
    Scope and Contents
    List of interested schools, accepted and declined proposals, and press releases.
  - Luce Fund for Asian Studies Binder, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
    List of interested schools, accepted and declined proposals, and press releases
  - Questionnaire Binder (A-B), 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Allegheny College, Agnes Scott College, Albion College, Alma College, Amherst College, Antioch College, Augustana College, Austin College, Bard College, Bates College, Beloit College, Bennington College, Birmingham-Southern College, Bowdoin College, Bryn Mawr College, Bucknell University.
  - Questionnaire Binder (C), 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Carleton College, Centre College, Chatham College, Claremont McKenna College, Colby College, Colgate University, College of Saint Benedict, College of the Holy Cross, College of William and Mary, College of Wooster, Colorado College, Connecticut College, Cornell College.
  - Questionnaire Binder (D-F), 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Denison University, DePaw University, Dickinson College, Drew University, Earlham College, Eckerd College, Fairfield University, Franklin and Marshall College, Furman University.
  - Questionnaire Binder (G-J), 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Gettysburg College, Gordon College, Grinnell College, Guilford College, Gustavus Adolphus College, Hamilton College, Hampshire College, Hartwick College, Haverford College, Hiram College, Hollins College, Hobart and William Smith Colleges, Hope College, Illinois Wesleyan University, John Carroll University, Juniata College.
  - Questionnaire Binder (K-N), 1999-2002 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Kalamazoo College, Kenyon College, Knox College, Lafayette College, Lake Forest College, Lawrence University, Lewis and Clark College, Luther College, Macalester College, Marlboro College, Mary Washington College, Middlebury College, Mills College, Moravian College, Mount Holyoke College, New College of the University of South Florida.
  - Questionnaire Binder (O-R), 1999-2002 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Oberlin College, Occidental College, Oglethorpe University, Ohio Wesleyan University, Pitzer College, Pomona College, Randolph-Macon College, Randolph-Macon Women's College, Reed College, Rhodes College.
  - Questionnaire Binder (S-T), 1999-2002 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Sarah Lawrence College, Simon's Rock College of Bard, Skidmore College, Smith College, Southwestern University, St. Lawrence University, St. Mary's College of Maryland, St. Olaf College, Swarthmore College, Trinity College.
  - Questionnaire Binder (U-V), 1999-2002 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Union College, University of the Puget Sound, University of the South, Ursinus College, Vassar College.
  - Questionnaire Binder (W), 1999-2002 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Wabash College, Washington and Lee University, Wellesley College, Wesleyan University, Wesleyan University, Westminster College, Wheaton College, Whitman College, Willamette University, Whittier College, Williams College, Wittenberg University.
  - Grant Recipients, 1999-2010 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Survey Report, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Professors List, 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Keynote, Samuel Hideo Yamashita, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Guidelines, 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Site Visit Reports, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Positions Filled, 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Capstone Conference, 2007 October 12-14 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Blank Questionnaire Forms, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Proposals - Volume 1, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Bard College, Bates College, Bucknell University, Colby College, College of Holy Cross.
  - Proposals - Volume 2, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Colorado College, Dickinson College, Drew University, Earlham College, Eckerd College, Hamilton College, Hobart and William Smith Colleges.
  - Proposals - Volume 3, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    Oberlin College, Reed College, Smith College, Southwestern University, Union College, Ursinus College, Westminster College.
  - Proposals - Volume 1, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    Beloit College, Bucknell University, Carleton College, College of St. Benedict, St. John's University, Denison University, Dickinson College, Gettysburg College, Hobart and William Smith Colleges, Lake Forest College, Lawrence University.
  - Proposals, Volume 2, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    Lewis and Clark College, Middlebury College, Mills College, New College of the University of South Florida, Occidental College, Pitzer College, Sarah Lawrence College, Skidmore College, St. Mary's College of Maryland, Williams College.
  - Proposals, Volume 1, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    Beloit College, Claremont McKenna College, Colgate University, DePauw University, Earlham College, Gettysburg College, Hampshire College, Kalamazoo College, Kenyon College, Lake Forest College.
  - Proposals, Volume 2, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Macalester College, Mount Holyoke College, Southwestern University, St. Lawrence University, St. Olaf College, University of Puget Sound, Vassar College, Wesleyan University, Williamette University, Wittenberg University.
  - Proposals, Volume 1, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Augustana College, Bowdoin College, Claremont McKenna College, The College of William and Mary, Connecticut College, Drew University, Furman University, Grinnell College, Gustavus Adolphus College, Hampshire College.
  - Proposals, Volume 2, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Macalester College, Randolph-Macon Woman's College, St. Lawrence University, St. Mary's College of Maryland, University of the South Sewanee, Ursinus College, Vassar College, Washington and Lee University, Wellesley College, Wittenberg University.
- Luce Fund for Southeast Asian Studies, 1987-1991; 2; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
  - Proposals, Volume 1, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    Cornell University, Northern Illinois University, Ohio University.
  - Proposals, Volume 2, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    University of California, Berkeley, University of Hawaii, University of Michigan, Yale University.
  - Proposals and Budget Summaries, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    Cornell University, Northern Illinois University, Northwest Regional Consortium, Ohio University, University of California, Berkeley, University of Hawaii, University of Michigan, University of Wisconsin, Yale University.
  - Proposals, Volume 1, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    Cornell University, Northern Illinois University, Northwest Regional Consortium, Ohio University.
  - Proposals, Volume 2, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    University of California, Berkeley, University of Hawaii, University of Michigan, University of Wisconsin, Yale University.
  - Library Proposals (Third Round), 1991 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    Arizona State University, Northwest Regional Consortium.
  - Proposals, Volume 1, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    Arizona State University, Cornell University, Northern Illinois University, Northwest Regional Consortium, Ohio University.
  - Proposals, Volume 2, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    University of California, Berkeley, University of Hawaii, Manoa, University of Michigan University of Wisconsin-Madison, Yale University.